Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) / Cleaner made for Display (GPU) Drivers.(NVIDIA/AMD)

What it does is remove the display/GPU driver from device manager and remove the current and 
all precedent driver(s) from the Windows Driver store along with removing services from NVIDIA/AMD.

The current effect after you use this tool will be similar to if Windows was in a "Fresh Install" state.

This tool acts much like "Driver Sweeper"*, and has all the extra mentioned above.

If you have any problems installing an older driver or a newer one, give it a try as there are some reports that it fixes
those problems.

RECOMMENDED USAGE :

-The tool can be used in Normal mode but for absolute stability when using DDU, Safe Mode is 
always the best.

- We would like to gather feedback from everyone, tell us if it was successful or not. 

- Make a backup or a system restore. (but it should normally be pretty safe.)

-If you have or had a driver problem, and this tool helped you with some issues you were or are
currently experiencing, please share your result.

Keep in mind that NVIDIA, AMD, nor Microsoft can be held responsible for any damages 
to you or your computer and are in no way affiliates of DDU, or it's creators.
-------------------------------

Created By Wagnard.

Co-owner: Shady757

Tester : Dellon132

Logos : juanchacin

Huge Thanks to Jackalito for the donation of a AMD 7850.

Thanks to Helge Klein (http://helgeklein.com/setacl/) : for the permission to use his Program with DDU "SetAcl"

Huge Thanks for their time for testing : Gamer1291 (optimus), Octopuss (Amd Enduro) , nedooo` (took time debugging with me)
Extraordinary (Testing a bug fix)

Thanks to anyone who put their system at risk. (special thanks to Dellon132)

*DDU, it's creators and affiliates are in no way affiliated with Driver Sweeper, or it's creators.