Display Driver Uninstaller ("DDU") USER AGREEMENT

You become a user of DDU ("User") by using the DDU software. This Agreement takes effect as soon as you use the program to uninstall a driver.

By using DDU you agree to not accuse DDU or it's creators, and affiliates, of damaging or negatively affecting your PC.

By using DDU you acknowledge that NVIDIA ("NVIDIA, GeForce") nor Advanced Micro Devices ("AMD, Radeon") have
anything to do with this program, and in no way affiliates of DDU or it's creators.